

Software Developer seeking role in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#.NET, MVC, ADO.NET, WEB API, LINQ, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, AJAX, Angular JS, SQL Server



Current Designation: Software Developer -Dot Net Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Current Company: Ansh Systems Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#.NET, MVC, ADO.NET, WEB

API,LINQ,HTML,CSS,JavaScript,Jquery,AJAX,AngularJS,SQL Server

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 3-Jul-20 Last Modified: 23-Jun-20

Summary

I have 5+ yrs of experience with recognized industries in the field of application development using Microsoft Technologies. Expertise in .Net technologies such as C#, MVC, ADO.Net, WEB API, LINQ, SQL Server, Javascript, Jquery, Angular.

Work Experience

Ansh Systems as Software Developer -Dot Net

May 2020 to Till Date

Responsibilities:

A senior developer, Responsible for client interaction, Requirement Gathering, Analysis, Developed programming logics, Perform unit tests and fix bugs, Deployment.

Micro Excel as Software Developer

Mar 2016 to Mar 2017

Responsibilities:

A team member, Developed programming logics, Perform unit tests and fix bugs, Client Interaction, Deployment Product.

Reval Analytical Services as Software Developer

Aug 2014 to Feb 2016

Responsibilities:

A team member, Developed programming logics, Perform unit tests and fix bugs, Client Interaction, Deployment Product.

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from Vidya Pratishathans Institute of Information Technology in 2011

PG: MCA (Computers) from Sinhgad Institute Of Management and Computer Applications in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C#.NET, MVC	5	2020	5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)
ADO.NET, Web API		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
LINQ, Entity Framework		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
HTML, CSS		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
JavaScript, JQuery		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
AJAX, Angular		2014	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
sql server 2008/2012		2020	4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
MS OFFICE			
Angular	8	2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time